[
    {
        "question": "What permissions are needed to import leads and contacts to a Campaign?",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "Marketing user checkbox & profile",
        "choices": [
            "Marketing User permission set",
            "Marketing user profile",
            "Marketing user checkbox on user",
            "Marketing user checkbox & profile"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If the Org Wide Default is Public Read/Write, what feature in Salesforce is needed to restrict access to that object?",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "Profile",
        "choices": [
            "Role Hierarchy",
            "Page Layout",
            "Profile",
            "Record Type"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the ways leads can be captured with Salesforce? (Choose two answers)",
        "qtype": "multi_choice",
        "answer": [
            "Web to Lead",
            "Lead Import"
        ],
        "choices": [
            "Lead Import",
            "Lead Assignment",
            "Web to Lead",
            "Email to Lead"
        ]
    },
	{ 
        "question": "Which of the following fields CANNOT be a controlling field for Dependent Picklists?",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "Custom Multi-Select Picklist",
        "choices": [
            "Custom Multi-Select Picklist",
            "Standard Picklist",
            "Standard Checkbox",
            "Custom Picklist",
            "Custom Checkbox"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Sales Director wants to be alerted to deals that are greater than $1,000,000. Which tools can you use to achieve this?",
        "qtype": "multi_choice",
        "answer" : [
            "Big Deal Alerts",
            "Workflow - Create a workflow to send an email if an Opportunity amount is great than 1,000,000"
        ],
        "choices": [
            "Create a report and monitor it daily",
            "Workflow - Create a workflow to send an email if an Opportunity amount is great than 1,000,000",
            "Ask the Sales Director to create a list view which shows Opportunities greater than 1,000,000",
            "Big Deal Alerts"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you uninstall an App Exchange application once it has been deployed?",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "choices": [
            "No",
            "Yes"
        ]
    },
	{
        "question": "A users security token will be refreshed every time their password is changed.",
        "qtype": "true_false",
        "answer": "True",
        "choices": [
            "False",
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {          
        "question": "What is a Bucket Field?",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "Used in reports to categorise and group report values",
        "choices": [
            "Used in reports to categorise and group report values",
            "Used to group multiple workflows",
            "A custom field that can be created to group values",
            "A custom field that can be created to store a finite amount of values"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tab is automatically created when you create a custom object.",
        "qtype": "true_false",
        "answer": "False",
        "choices": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ]
    },
	{
        "question": "Standard picklist fields cannot be dependent fields",
        "qtype": "true_false",
        "answer": "True",
        "choices": [
            "False",
            "True"
        ]
    },
	{
        "question": "Which of the following are standard Salesforce Objects?",
        "qtype": "multi_choice",
        "answer": [
            "Pricebook",
            "Contract",
            "Opportunity Product"
        ],
        "choices": [
            "Opportunity Product",
            "Pricebook",
            "Ticket",
            "Contract"
        ]
    },
	{
        "question": "A user can save a record even if a data validation error message appears.",
        "qtype": "true_false",
        "answer": "False",
        "choices": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these objects can you map a field to on lead conversion?",
        "qtype": "multi_choice",
        "answer": [
            "Contacts",
            "Account",
            "Opportunity"
        ],
        "choices": [
            "Account",
            "Contacts",
            "Cases",
            "Opportunities"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Is it possible for a user to own a record and not see it?",
        "qtype": "true_false",
        "answer": "True",
        "choices": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ]
    },
	{
        "question": "A customer service manager would like to automatically assign cases to the most appropriate agent to handle the request. What feature could be used?",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "Case Assignment Rules",
        "choices": [
            "Case Assignment Rules",
            "Case Escalation Rules",
            "Email to Case",
            "Web to Case"
        ]
    },
	{
        "question": "What can an email template contain?",
        "qtype": "multi_choice",
        "answer": [
            "Attached File",
            "Text",
            "Merge Field"
        ],
        "choices": [
            "Macro",
            "Text",
            "Attached File",
            "Merge Field"
        ]
    },
	{
        "question": "Which profiles listed are a standard Profile? Select all that apply",
        "qtype": "multi_choice",
        "answer": [
            "Marketing User",
            "Standard User",
            "Contract Manager"
        ],
        "choices": [
            "Contract Manager",
            "Standard User",
            "Marketing User",
            "Invoice Manager"
        ]
    },
	{
        "question": "When a lead is converted, it becomes an Account, Contact, and Opportunity (unless you opt out of creating an opportunity)",
        "qtype": "true_false",
        "answer": "True",
        "choices": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the different types of Sharing Rules?",
        "qtype": "multi_choice",
        "answer": [
            "Case Sharing Rules",
            "Lead Sharing Rules",
            "Custom Object Sharing Rules",
            "Account Sharing Rules"
        ],
        "choices": [
            "Case Sharing Rules",
            "Lead Sharing Rules",
            "Solution Sharing Rules",
            "Account Sharing Rules",
            "Custom Object Sharing Rules"
        ]
    },
	{
        "question": "What is conditional highlighting for reports?",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "Shows you visual highlights depending on a threshold",
        "choices": [
            "You can set conditions that when met, will report the calculated fields",
            "Lets you make calculations on custom fields",
            "Shows you visual highlights depending on a threshhold",
            "Users can highlight particularly interesting parts of a report"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these is not a Salesforce feature?",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "Email to Lead",
        "choices": [
            "Email to Lead",
            "Web to Lead",
            "Web to Case",
            "Email to Case"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can you make a field required? (Select all that apply)",
        "qtype": "multi_choice",
        "answer": [
            "Page Layouts",
            "Validation Rules",
            "Field Edit Page"
        ],
        "choices": [
            "Workflow Rule",
            "Page Layouts",
            "Validation Rules",
            "Field Edit page",
            "Record Type"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a roll-up summary field?",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "A roll-up summary field is a custom field that aggregates child record information into the parent record",
        "choices": [
            "A roll-up summary field lets you rollback the data that was changed last week",
            "The roll-up summary field gives you a summary of the data type and object relationship",
            "A roll-up summary field is a custom field that aggregates child record information into the parent record",
            "The roll-up summary field is accessible via the API"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you delete a user?",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "You cannot delete a Salesforce User",
        "choices": [
            "Using an external application",
            "Going to their profile and clicking the delete button",
            "Deleting all information from their profile",
            "You cannot delete a Salesforce User"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "When converting a Lead, what values are transferred to the Opportunity?",
        "qtype": "multi_choice",
        "answer": [
            "Close Date = Today",
            "Stage = First stage in list"
        ],
        "choices": [
            "Close Date = Today",
            "Amount = Lead Amount",
            "Stage = First stage in list",
            "Close Date = Last day in fiscal quarter"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A Marketing manager would like to generate a list of contacts for a mailing list. What type of report would be the most appropriate to use:",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "Tabular",
        "choices": [
            "Summary",
            "Matrix",
            "Tabular",
            "Mailing"
        ]
    },
	{
        "question": "Is it possible to share a custom object record manually?",
        "qtype": "true_false",
        "answer": "True",
        "choices": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these actions can be triggered from a Workflow?",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "Field Update, New Task, Email Sent, Outbound Message",
        "choices": [
            "Email Sent, Field U`pdate",
            "Field Update, Email Sent, APEX Trigger, New Task",
            "Field Update, New Task, Email Sent, Outbound Message",
            "Create Object, New `Task, Email Sent,"
        ]
    },
	{
        "question": "Field Level Security or Page Layout can be used to make a field required ",
        "qtype": "true_false",
        "answer": "False",
        "choices": [
            "False",
            "True"
        ]
    },
	{
        "question": "Data loss can occur when changing fields from the following types (choose all that are)",
        "qtype": "multi_choice",
        "answer": [
            "Changing from a multi-select picklist to any other type",
            "Changing from a checkbox to any other type of field",
            "To a Number field from any other type of field"
        ],
        "choices": [
            "Changing from a multi-select picklist to any other type",
            "Changing from a checkbox to any other type of field",
            "To a Number field from any other type of field",
            "Changing from a Number field to a Text field"
        ]
    },
    {          
        "question": "What should a system administrator use to disable access to a custom application for a group of users?",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "Profiles",
        "choices": [
            "Profiles",
            "Sharing Rules",
            "Web Tabs",
            "Page Layouts"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Formulas ignore Field Level Security settings",
        "qtype": "true_false",
        "answer": "True",
        "choices": [
            "False",
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {           
        "question": "An Approval Process begins when a record is..",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "Submitted for Approval",
        "choices": [
            "Created",
            "Edited",
            "Saved",
            "Submitted for Approval"
        ]
    },
	{
        "question": "A system administrator needs to restrict users ability to view a dashboard. How can this be accomplished?",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "Restrict the access to the folder that the dashboard is located",
        "choices": [
            "Restrict the access to the folder that the source report is located",
            "Restrict the access to the folder that the dashboard is located",
            "Create a sharing rule to restrict the access",
            "Disable access to the dashboard on the users profile"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many objects may be imported or updated using the data loader in one operation?",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "1",
        "choices": [
            "10",
            "Unlimited",
            "1",
            "5"
        ]
    },
	{
        "question": "What is the maximum number of Components available on a Dashboard?",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "20",
        "choices": [
            "10",
            "20",
            "50",
            "5"
        ]
    },
    { 
        "question": "A user would like to generate a list of contacts for a mailing list. What type of report would be the most appropriate to use?",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "Tabular",
        "choices": [
            "Joined",
            "Summary",
            "Tabular",
            "Matrix"
        ]
    },
	{
        "question": "In which scenarios will the sharing button appear?",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "When the sharing model for the object is private or public read only",
        "choices": [
            "It will always appear",
            "When the sharing model for the object is public read/write",
            "When the sharing model for the object is private",
            "When the sharing model for the object is private or public read only"
        ]
    },
	{
        "question": "To track revenue gain or loss based on currency fluctuations, you must implement what feature?",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "Advanced Currency Management",
        "choices": [
            "Multi-Currency",
            "Sandbox",
            "Advanced Currency Management",
            "Territory Management"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gauge and metric dashboard component types are based on what from a report?",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "Grand Total",
        "choices": [
            "Grand Total",
            "Average",
            "Chart",
            "Sum"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Workflow cannot be triggered upon import.",
        "qtype": "true_false",
        "answer": "False",
        "choices": [
            "False",
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Workflow can be triggered upon import.",
        "qtype": "true_false",
        "answer": "True",
        "choices": [
            "False",
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {                
        "question": "You can make fields visible, read-only, and required using Page Layouts.",
        "qtype": "true_false",
        "answer": "True",
        "choices": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a Junction Object?",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "A Many-to-Many relationship created with two lookup master-detail relationship",
        "choices": [
            "A Many-to-Many relationship created with two lookup relationships",
            "A Many-to-Many relationship created with two lookup master-detail relationship",
            "A standard object",
            "An object type to connect external web services"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Why should you consider using the Import Wizard over the Data Loader?",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "If you require some De-Duplication",
        "choices": [
            "You need field auto-mapping functionality",
            "If you require some De-Duplication",
            "If you need to import more than 1,000,000 records",
            "If you need to import to custom objects only"
        ]
    },
	{
        "question": "A user can still report on a field they have access to, if it is hidden from the page layout",
        "qtype": "true_false",
        "answer": "True",
        "choices": [
            "False",
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What should a system administrator consider before importing a set of records into Salesforce?",
        "qtype": "multi_choice",
        "answer": [
            "The import file should include a record owner for each record",
            "Data should be de-duplicated in the import file prior to import"
        ],
        "choices": [
            "Data should be de-duplicated in the import file prior to import",
            "The import file should include a record owner for each record",
            "Currency field values will default to the personal currency of the record owner",
            "Validation rules are not triggered when importing data using the import wizard"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A customer service manager would like to automatically assign cases to the most appropriate agent to handle the request. What feature could be used?",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "Case Assignment Rules",
        "choices": [
            "Email to Case",
            "Case Escalation Rules",
            "Case Assignment Rules",
            "Web to Case"
        ]
    },
	{
        "question": "You can use standard reports when creating Dashboards?",
        "qtype": "true_false",
        "answer": "False",
        "choices": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of report cannot be used to populate a chart in a dashboard?",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "Tabular",
        "choices": [
            "Summary",
            "Matrix",
            "Tabular"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "When are Data validation Rules Enforced?",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "Upon saving a record",
        "choices": [
            "Upon editing a field",
            "Upon opening a record",
            "Upon closing the record",
            "Upon saving a record"
        ]
    },
	{
        "question": "A Sales Manager would like to get a report of opportunities grouped by sales stage. What kind of report meet this requirement: ",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "Summary",
        "choices": [
            "Matrix",
            "Tabular",
            "Summary",
            "All Salesforce Reports"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A sales manager would like to view a dashboard from the perspective of different users and switch between users without editing the dashboard, how would an administrator enable this?",
        "qtype": "multi_choice",
        "answer": [
            "Create the dashboard as a dynamic dashboard",
            "Grant the sales manager the 'View my Teams Dashboard' permission"
        ],
        "choices": [
            "Grant the sales manager the 'View my Teams Dashboard' permission",
            "Grant the sales manager the 'Drag-and-Drop Dashboard builder' permission",
            "Create the dashboard as a dynamic dashboard",
            "Grant the sales manager the 'Manage Dynamic Dashboards' permission"
        ]
    },
	{
        "question": "You can restrict a profiles view to a certain field by using which feature?",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "Field Level Security",
        "choices": [
            "Profiles",
            "Roles",
            "Field Level Security",
            "Permission Sets"
        ]
    },
	{ 
        "question": "All of the following objects may have a queue EXCEPT ",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "Accounts",
        "choices": [
            "Leads",
            "Cases",
            "Accounts",
            "Custom Objects"
       ]
    },   
	{
        "question": "Fields which are hidden using Field-Level-Security are still subject to Validation Rules?",
        "qtype": "true_false",
        "answer": "True",
        "choices": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {  
        "question": "What is true about dynamic dashboards: ",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "A dynamic dashboard will show data according to the user's security settings",
        "choices": [
            "In dynamic dashboards, the source reports used can vary according to the user",
            "A dynamic dashboard will show data according to the user's security settings",
            "If a user wants to customise the dashboard, they should use a dynamic dashboard",
            "A dynamic dashboard will refresh automatically several times a day"
        ]
    },
    {           
        "question": "A roll-up summary field requires a Master Detail relationship",
        "qtype": "true_false",
        "answer": "True",
        "choices": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You want to give a profile access to a custom object. What would be the best way to do this?",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "Clone a standard profile and grant additional access",
        "choices": [
            "Create a permission set and assign it to relevant users",
            "Clone a standard profile and grant additional access",
            "Create a new profile and grant access",
            "Edit a standard profile"
        ]
    },
    {	 
        "question": "Which statements about custom summary formulas in reports is true?",
        "qtype": "multi_choice",
        "answer": [
            "Custom summary formulas can reference a formula field within a report",
            "Custom summary formulas can be used in a report built from a custom report type"
        ],
        "choices": [
            "Reports can be grouped by a custom summary formula result",
            "Custom summary formulas can be used in a report built from a custom report type",
            "Custom summary formulas can reference a formula field within a report",
            "Custom summary formulas can reference another custom summary formula"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Quotes & Opportunities are part of which cloud product?",
        "qtype": "single_choice",
        "answer": "Sales Cloud",
        "choices": [
            "Analytics Cloud",
            "Sales Cloud",
            "Marketing Cloud",
            "Service Cloud"
        ]
    }
]